Welcome to Expense Agent video series.
In this video, we will show how to use
projects and tasks into web app.
So, before we start to explain it, we
want to uh give a little bit more light
how you can set up and what you need to
do and how you can use it. First,
administrator can decide if uh projects
and tasks will be visible in web app or
not. By default, they're not visible,
but you can easily enable. And then,
when you enable as administrator and
enable you can decide which level you
want to expose to submitters. All
projects and tasks or only there when uh
this submitter is assigned. So, this is
uh on control administrator how we will
expose. And then, when we submit and
everything, uh submitter cannot post ex-
expense report and cannot post and
cannot make a project ledger entry
because submitter doesn't have easy
central license. So, you must have easy
central license. You must be controller
or accountant. So, you you need to
review uh to check all dimensions and
then to post. So, submitter can assign
expense to the project, but cannot post.
So, now let's see how it works in the
practice.
Mhm.
>> Yeah, so I'll show you the example where
an expense user is logged into the web
app and there they want to submit an
expen- expense and associate it with a
project. So, I've already created an
expense report where I've uploaded the
receipt and now it
it has already extracted the information
and in under the categorization tab, we
have an option for projects.
And this is where I get to choose which
project this expense belongs to. So, in
this case, I'm selecting the project
which I want this expense to go into and
also against the project task. Once I
have done, I can save the changes and
the same change will reflect in BC
under the expense report line.
To show you uh what happened inside BC,
uh we can look at first how the setup
was done. So, it's in this configuration
wizard of expense agent.
Uh
under project tracking, we have
activated the project tracking and the
project visibility was set to all
project in this case. You can also
choose it to use assigned projects. So,
only the
only expense user will see their own
projects.
Today, the expense user is linked to an
employee and the employee is in turn
linked to a resource. So, in this case,
in my expense user card, I can see how
the expense user is linked to a resource
and the employee.
This is how we establish connection
between the expense user and the
resource.
>> Completely
design is made with assumption that
submitter knows a specific project. But
even if submitter doesn't know specific
project, controller still has a chance
to add this manually in a busy central.
So, we have full control from web app or
from busy central.
So, thank you for watching this video.